National Women's Health Network records SSC.MS.00360
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IX. PROJECTS, PROGRAMS, AND REFORM EFFORTS, 1963-2007
  - Clearinghouse
    - Project: Consumer guide of national non-profit women's health organizations (proposed), 1997-98
      - Survey responses
        - American Anorexia Bulimia Association (AABA) (Box 131A, Folder 2)
        - American Anorexia Nervosa and Related Eating Disorders (Box 131A, Folder 3)
        - American Autoimmune Related Diseases Association, Inc. (Box 131A, Folder 4)
        - American Heart Association (Box 131A, Folder 5)
        - American Society for Reproductive Medicine (Box 131A, Folder 6)
        - The Arthritis Foundation (Box 131A, Folder 7)
        - Asians and Pacific Islanders for Reproductive Health (Box 131A, Folder 8)
        - Association of Reproductive Health Professionals (ARHP) (Box 131A, Folder 9)
        - Boston Women's Health Book Collective (Box 131A, Folder 10)
        - Center for Complementary and Alternative Medicine Research in Women's Health (Box 131A, Folder 11)
        - Center for Reproductive Health Law and Policy (CRLP) (Box 131A, Folder 12)
        - Center for Women's Health Research, School of Nursing, University of Washington (Box 131A, Folder 13)
        - The Compassionate Friends, Inc., (TCF) (Box 131A, Folder 14)
        - DES Action USA (Box 131A, Folder 15)
        - Endometriosis Association (Box 131A, Folder 16)
        - Environmental Health Network on California (EHN) (Box 131A, Folder 17)
        - Federation of Feminist Women's Health Centers (Box 131A, Folder 18)
        - Hysterectomy Educational Resources and Services Foundation (Box 131A, Folder 19)
        - International Women's Health Coalition (IWHC) (Box 131A, Folder 20)
        - Interstitial Cystitis Association (ICA) (Box 131A, Folder 21)
        - Interstitial Cystitis Network (ICN) (Box 131A, Folder 22)
        - Jacobs Institute of Women's Health (Box 131B, Folder 1)
        - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) (Box 131B, Folder 2)
        - National Academy on Women's Health Medical Education (Box 131B, Folder 3)
        - National Alliance of Breast Cancer Organizations (Box 131B, Folder 4)
        - National Asian Women's Health Organization (NAWHO) (Box 131B, Folder 5)
        - National Association for Continence (NAFC) (Box 131B, Folder 6)
        - National Association of Women's Health Professionals (Box 131B, Folder 7)
        - National Black Women's Health Project (Box 131B, Folder 8)
        - National Chronic Fatigue Syndrome and Fibromyalgia Association (Box 131B, Folder 9)
        - National Coalition against Domestic Violence (Box 131B, Folder 10)
        - National Depressive and Manic Depressive Association (Box 131B, Folder 11)
        - National Foundation for Depressive Illness (NAFDI) (Box 131B, Folder 12)
        - National Health Care Anti-Fraud Association (NHCAA) (Box 131B, Folder 13)
        - National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health (Box 131B, Folder 14)
        - National Latina Health Organization (NLHO) (Box 131B, Folder 15)
        - National Lesbian and Gay Health Association (Box 131B, Folder 16)
        - National Lymphedema Network (NLN) (Box 131B, Folder 17)
        - National Mental Health Association (NMHA) (Box 131B, Folder 18)
        - National Resource Center on Domestic Violence (NRC) (Box 131B, Folder 19)
        - Native American Women's Health Education Resource Center (Box 131B, Folder 20)
        - North American Menopause Society (Box 131C, Folder data_value_missing_7a04fbc1f6d4a2c0053789a69e054840)
        - Pacific Institute for Women's Health (Box 131C, Folder 2)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (PPFA) (Box 131C, Folder 3)
        - Public Citizen's Health Research Group (PCHRG) (Box 131C, Folder 4)
        - Reproductive Health Technologies Project (RHTP) (Box 131C, Folder 5)
        - RESOLVE (Box 131C, Folder 6)
        - Society for the Advancement of Women's Health Research (Box 131C, Folder 7)
        - TMJ Association (Box 131C, Folder 8)
        - Vulvar Pain Foundation (Box 131C, Folder 9)
        - Women's AIDS Network (WAN) (Box 131C, Folder 10)
        - Women's Cancer Resource Center (Box 131C, Folder 11)
    - Statistics, 1986-91 (Box 132, Folder 1-6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-96 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Consumer protection
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1980-81 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Federal Drug Administration (FDA)
      - Committees
        - Anesthetic and Life Support Drugs, 1979-82 (Box 133, Folder 2)
        - Consumer Advisory, 1979-84 (Box 133, Folder 3)
        - Endocrinology and Metabolic Drug Advisory, 1991, 1997 (Box 133, Folder 4-5)
        - Fertility and Maternal Health Drug Advisory
          - 1979-83 (Box 133, Folder 6-3)
          - 1984-90 (Box 134, Folder 1-5)
        - Genetic Drugs Advisory (2 v.), 1991 (Box 135)
        - Immunology and Obstetrics-Gynecology Advisory, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 1)
        - Nonprescription Drugs, Reproductive Health, Anti-Infective Drugs, and antiviral Drugs Advisory Committees joint meeting, 1996
          - Background material (1 v.) (Box 135)
          - Days 1-3 (Box 136, Folder 1-2)
          - NDMA submission to the Committee (Box 136, Folder 3)
        - Patient education, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 4)
        - Psychopharmacologic Drugs Advisory 1984 (Box 136, Folder 5)
        - Reproductive Health Advisory, 2002-03 (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Consumer Exchange meetings, 1979-1983 (Box 136, Folder 7)
      - Contraceptive Efficacy Study, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 1-1A)
      - Correspondence
        - Goyan, Jere (Commissioner), 1979-80 (Box 137, Folder 2)
        - Haire, Doris to FDA on cesarean section, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 3)
        - Kennedy, Donald (commissioner), 1979 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - Direct to Consumer Advertising, 1978-83 (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - Drug Regulation Reform Act, 1978-80 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - Drug safety screening, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - Food and drug labeling, 1978-79 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Health and the Older Woman: Information packet, 1988-89 (Box 137, Folder 9-9A)
      - Medical device standards and safety, 1978-81 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Medication guides, 1993-94 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Medtech Diagnostics premarket approval application (1 v.), 1991 (Box 138)
      - Misbranded oral contraceptives, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Obstetrics and gynecology Devices Panel meeting (1 v.), 1991 (Box 138)
      - Office of Consumer Affairs
        - Consumer Consortium, 1983-84 (Box 139, Folder 1)
        - Consumer Consortium meetings, 1981-84 (Box 139, Folder 2)
        - Consumer guidelines, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 3)
        - Consumer representatives, 1978-96 (Box 139, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1979-84 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Olestra, 1996-99 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Over the counter drugs
        - Petition to the FDA, 1982 (Box 140, Folder 1)
        - Pregnancy/nursing warning labels, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 2)
        - Public Hearing on Over-the Counter Drug Products, 2000 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Package inserts, 1978-82 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Patient education, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Petitions to the FDA collected at American Public Health Association (APHA) meetings, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Pharmaceutical drug exports, 1983-84 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Prescription Drug information For Patients: Developing Useful Information (Workshop), 1996 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Public Participation Program, 1979 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Technical Assistance Project, n.d. (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Watchdog proposals, 1978-79 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Weight Control Drug Products for Over the Counter Human Use, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Women's Health Initiative: Information packet, 1987-89 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974-99, n.d. (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Product liability
      - Congressional acts and bills
        - Product Liability Act (S. 100): Bill text and hearing, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 7)
        - Product Liability Bills
          - Senate 44
            - Analysis and its effect, 1983-84, n.d. (Box 141, Folder 8)
            - Hearing Report, 1983 (Box 141, Folder 9)
            - Testimony
              - NWHN, 1983 (Box 141, Folder 10)
              - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 1)
            - Statements in opposition, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 2)
            - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 3)
          - H.R. 115, 1987-88 (Box 142, Folder 4)
        - Unfair Product Liability Standards (H.R. 27290), 1983 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Product liability statement (NWHN), 1984 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Strategy meetings, 1984-85 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-88 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - SPAN [Stop Patient Abuse Now] litigation, 2001 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Dalkon Shield/Intrauterine devices
    - Articles and clippings, 1974-90, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 1-7)
    - Attorney lists and fees, 1986-88, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Chronology, 1987, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Copper-7, 1973-88, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 10-11)
    - CU-380a, 1981-88, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1985-89, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 13-16)
    - Financial materials, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - International
      - Correspondence, 1985-86 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Mailing lists, 1984-86, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Notes, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Printed material, 1985-86, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Legal materials
      [see also Litigation Information Service - Dalkon Shield]
      - Citizen's Petition to FDA, 1983
        - Attachments (Box 144, Folder 6)
        - Petition (Box 144, Folder 7)
        - Request for advisory opinion (Box 144, Folder 8)
        - Research reports (Box 144, Folder 9)
        - Statistical report (Box 144, Folder 10)
      - Claims against A.H. Robins, 1987-88 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Court cases v. A.H. Robins
        - Gantner, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 2)
        - Morgan, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 3)
        - NWHN et al (class action) 1981-82 (Box 145, Folder 4)
        - Strempke, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 5)
        - Vasseur, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous, 1972-86, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Motion to dismiss Chapter 11 case, A. H. Robins, 1985-88 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Media and outreach
      - "The Dalkon Shield" (booklet), 1985 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - "Danger sheet" (English, Portuguese, French, Spanish), 1986 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Film: "IUDS Calculating the Risks," 1985 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Information packet, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Media plan, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Press campaign, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Press conference, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Press releases and statements,1981-87, n.d.
        - NWHN, 1981-87, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous, 1984-86, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Radio and television, 1985, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Richmond Rally, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-87 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Notes, 1988, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Organizations
      - Action Alert for Women, 1986 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust, 1988-92 (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - Dalkon Shield Information Network, 1987-90 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - Dalkon Shield Victims Association, 1986 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - FDA, 1979 (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - International Dalkon Shield Victims Education Association, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Medical Claims Consultants, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - Official Committee of Dalkon Shield Claimants, 1988 (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - Protocol and registry, 1984-85 (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - Referrals, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 23)
  - Depo-Provera Project
    - Animal [dogs] studies with Depo-Provera and Progesterone, 1981, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Consent forms (sample), 1995, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence
      - Depo-Provera lawsuits, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Internal memos (NWHN), 1979-82 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Letters from members of Congress, 1980-81 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Letters to members of Congress and Administration, 1981 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Letters from doctors, 1977-82 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Norsigian, Judy, 1979-82 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Pro Depo-Provera letters, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - Requests for information, 1980-86 (Box 147, Folder 10-11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-93 (Box 148, Folder 1-3)
    - Department of Health and Human Services, Public Health Service, Food and Drug Administration, Fertility and Maternal Health Drugs Advisory Committee
      - Depo-Provera C-150, Advisory Committee Brochure (2 v), 1992 (Box 148)
      - Transcript of proceedings (1v), 1992 (Box 148)
    - Depo-Provera: What Is the Real Debate? An Alternative Framework of Analysis, 1980 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - The Depo-Provera Debate: Hearings before the Senate Subcommittee on Population (U.S. House of Representatives), 1978 (Box 148)
    - Depo-Provera patient and physician information, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Endorsements, 1982, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Federal Drug Administration Public Board of Inquiry (Upjohn Company)
      - Background, 1981, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence
        - Upjohn Company, 1980-85 (Box 149, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1979-82 (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Pathology reports, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - Prehearing conference, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      - Procedures and timetable (Upjohn's), 1981 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - Reimbursement for participation, 1979-80 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      - Steptoe & Johnson (counsel for NWHN): correspondence and miscellaneous documents, 1980-83 (Box 149, Folder 10-12)
      - Submissions (non NWHN)
        - Upjohn, 1979 (Box 150, Folder 1-2)
        - World Health Organization, 1978-82 (Box 150, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous, 1980-83 (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - Testimony (Upjohn), 1982 (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - Transcripts
        - Depo-Provera for Contraception: Exception to Report of Public Board of Inquiry and Brief for the Upjohn Company(2v), 1985 (Box 151)
        - Depo Provera for Contraception: Information on Depo Provera: Responses to the Board's Questions (the Upjohn Company), 1982 (Box 151, Folder 1)
        - Depo Provera Sterile Aqueous Suspension: Availability of Public Board of Inquiry Decision, Including Findings and Conclusions (1v), 1984 (Box 151)
        - Official transcript of proceedings (5 v), 1983 (Box 152)
        - Post Hearing Brief for the National Center for Drugs and Biotics, 1983 (Box 152, Folder 1)
        - Supplemental Brief of the national Center for Drugs and Biologics (Box 152, Folder 2)
        - Rebuttal (Upjohn), 1983 (Box 152, Folder 3)
        - Reproductive studies by Upjohn), 1977 (Box 153, Folder 1)
        - Responses to the FDA letter (Upjohn), 1978-82 (Box 153, Folder 2)
        - Response of the Center for Drugs and Biologics to the Exceptions of the Upjohn Company, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 3)
        - "Response to Questions on Monkey Tissue Specimens and Slides" (Upjohn), 1983 (Box 153, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous orders, reports, notices, and summaries, 1979-85 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - Witnesses
        - Communications, 1982 (Box 153, Folder 6)
        - Potential witnesses and "cast of characters," 1979-81 (Box 153, Folder 7)
        - Testimonies, 1983
          - Anello, Charles (Box 153, Folder 8)
          - Corea, Gena (Box 153, Folder 9)
          - Done, Alan (Box 153, Folder 10)
          - Gross, M. Adrian (Box 153, Folder 11)
          - Hatcher, Robert (Box 154, Folder 1)
          - Hoover, Robert N. (Box 154, Folder 2)
          - Jones, Vickie (Box 154, Folder 3)
          - Kornebrot, Carol (Box 154, Folder 4)
          - Norris, Henry (Box 154, Folder 5)
          - Rhodes, Christopher (Box 154, Folder 6)
          - Richwald, Gary A. (Box 154, Folder 7)
          - Shearer, Ruth (Box 154, Folder 8)
          - Silverstein, Diane (Box 154, Folder 9)
          - Sobel, Solomon (Box 154, Folder 10)
          - Temple, Robert (Box 154, Folder 11)
          - Wolfe, Sidney M. (Box 154, Folder 12)
          - Miscellaneous additional testimonies and rebuttals (Box 154, Folder 13)
      - Wolfe (Sidney): article, letter, critique, and analysis, 1977 (Box 154, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1978-84, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Hatcher Report: A Descriptive Analysis of Women Using Depo-Provera at Grady Memorial Hospital Family Planning Clinic 1974 and 1978, n.d. 1983 (Box 155)
    - House Subcommittee on General Oversight and Investigations Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, 1987 (Box 155)
    - House Subcommittee on International Economic Policy and Trade (Committee on Foreign Affairs): Stephen Minkin (NWHN consultant) testimony)
      - Articles by Stephen Minkin, 1979-81, n.d. (Box 155)
      - Conversation between Minkin and Haroon Rahman, 1979 (Box 155)
      - Correspondence, 1980-81 (Box 155)
      - Transcripts, 1980-83 (Box 155)
    - International and export to third world countries
      - Agency for International Development (U.S. International Development Cooperation Agency), 1979-81, n.d. (Box 155)
      - Archer, Elizabeth: "Injectable Long-Acting Progestagens and Their Place in Contraception in Some Developing Countries," 1985 (Box 155)
      - Articles and clippings, 1978-86, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 1-2)
      - Asian (Second) Regional Workshop on Injectable Contraceptives, 1982 (Box 156, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1980-83 (Box 156, Folder 4)
      - Countries
        - Australia and New Zealand, 1977, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 5)
        - Canada
          - Articles and clippings, 1980-82 (Box 156, Folder 6)
          - "Depo-Provera: A Shot in the Dark" (Quebec Public Interest Group), 1982 (Box 156)
        - England
          - Articles and clippings, 1979-83 (Box 156, Folder 8)
          - Department of Health and Social Security (A public hearing under the provisions of the Medicines Act, 1968) (London), 1983 (Box 156, Folder 9)
        - India, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 10)
        - Jamaica, West Indies, 1980-81 (Box 156, Folder 11)
        - Kenya, 1981 (Box 156, Folder 12)
        - Philippines, 1981 (Box 156, Folder 13)
        - Thailand, 1980-81, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 14)
        - Zimbabwe, 1981 (Box 156, Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous, 1982, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 16)
      - "Export of Hazardous Products" (Hearings before the Subcommittee on International Economic Policy and Trade of the Committee on Foreign Affairs, House of Representatives), 1980
      - Printed official transcript (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - Statements and reports (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - Federal Policy on Export of Banned Substances, 1980-81 (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - Interagency Working Group on a Hazardous Substances Export Policy (Government Accountability Project), 1980 (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation (endorsement of Depo-Provera), 1980 (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - National Alliance of Third World Journalists, 1987-88 (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - "The Shot Felt Round the World," n.d. (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - Swenson, Norma: Testimony Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs (House of Representatives), 1987 (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - World Bank, 1978-80 (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - World Health Organization, 1982, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Media and outreach
      [see also SERIES VII. CORRESPONDENCE - Subjects- Phil Donahue Show responses]
      - Articles and clippings, 1978-892 (Box 157, Folder 11-12)
      - Film: "The Ultimate Test animal," 1985 (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - NWHN
        - Depo packet, 1979-80 (Box 158, Folder 2)
        - Press releases, news alerts, radio announcements, and statements, 1979-84, n.d. 4 Press conference and press kit, 1979-83 (Box 158, Folder 3)
        - Media contacts, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 5)
        - The Depo-Provera Debate: a Report by the National Women's Health Network, 1983-85 (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - Rooks, Judith: Talk on Depo-Provera for National Family Planning and Reproductive Association, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - Skit: "The Moral Majority Salutes International Women's Day,",n.d. (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Organizations (Box 158)
      - California Institute of Medical Ethics, 1982 (Box 159, Folder 1)
      - Coalition to Stop Depo-Provera, 1982 (Box 159, Folder 2)
      - Consumer Exchange, 1979 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - Institute for the Study of Medical Ethics, 1978-79 (Box 159, Folder 4)
      - Women's health groups, 1978-80, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Petitions, 1981, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Pro Depo-Provera material, 1980 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Proposal and request for funding, 1979, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Registry
      - Statistical analysis, 1979-82 (Box 159, Folder 9)
      - Worksheet, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 10)
      - Client information: Lists, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 1)
        Conditions Governing Access
        [CLOSED UNTIL 2065]
      - Correspondence
        - Letters without questionnaires, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 2)
        - Letters and questionnaires, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 3)
        - Letters answered
          - Alabama - Wyoming, 1979-85 (Box 160, Folder 4-5)
          - Miscellaneous, 1983-86 (Box 160, Folder 6)
      - Registry questionnaires
        - California registry, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 1)
        - Class action suit, 1980-84 (Box 161, Folder 2)
        - Class action victims, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 3)
        - Diagnosis
          - Contraception, 1983-85 (Box 161, Folder 4)
          - Dermatitis, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 5)
          - Dysfunctional uterine bleeding, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 6)
          - Endometriosis, 1983-83 (Box 161, Folder 7)
          - Infertility, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 8)
          - Menopause, 1985 (Box 161, Folder 9)
          - Menstruation
            - Prevention, 1985 (Box 161, Folder 10)
            - Regulate, 1983-85 (Box 161, Folder 11)
            - Start, 1985 (Box 161, Folder 12)
          - Miscarriage, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 13)
          - Ovarian cysts, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 14)
          - Ovulation prevention, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 15)
          - PMS, 1985-87 (Box 161, Folder 16)
          - Precocious puberty, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 17)
          - Pregnancy determination, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 18)
        - Illinois registry, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 19)
        - Non-registry victims, n.d. (Box 161, Folder 20)
        - Victims in registry, 1983 (Box 162, Folder 1)
        - Don't want to be in suit, 1983 (Box 162, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1983-85, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Select Committee on Population (House of Representatives): 1978 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - "Toxic Substances: Decisions and Values" (Ethical and Value Implications of Science and Technology Program of the National Science Foundation), 1979 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - United Presbyterian Church shareholder resolution to Upjohn Company, 1982-83 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Work plan, notes, and chronology, 1982-83 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Diethystilbestrol (DES) Project
    - Animal feed additives, 1979-80 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Bibliographies, 1974, 1980 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Center for Disease control/NWHN DES evaluation survey [WESAT research group], 2001-02 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1979-98 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - DES Daughters Identification Project, 1978-80 (Box 164, Folder 5)
      [see also Legal issues and litigation - Payton et al v. Abbott]
    - DES Granddaughters, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 6)